{
  "title": "Greek Mythology",
  "topic": "66fec2c9b6950e88826fe010",
  "difficulty": "medium",
  "num_questions": 10,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is the king of the Greek gods?",
      "options": [
        "Hades",
        "Zeus",
        "Poseidon",
        "Apollo"
      ],
      "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the winged horse in Greek mythology?",
      "options": [
        "Cerberus",
        "Chimera",
        "Pegasus",
        "Hydra"
      ],
      "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the goddess of wisdom and warfare?",
      "options": [
        "Artemis",
        "Athena",
        "Demeter",
        "Aphrodite"
      ],
      "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hero is known for his 12 labors?",
      "options": [
        "Hercules",
        "Perseus",
        "Theseus",
        "Achilles"
      ],
      "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the god of the sea?",
      "options": [
        "Hades",
        "Zeus",
        "Poseidon",
        "Hermes"
      ],
      "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the underworld in Greek mythology?",
      "options": [
        "Elysium",
        "Hades",
        "Olympus",
        "Tartarus"
      ],
      "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the messenger of the gods?",
      "options": [
        "Apollo",
        "Ares",
        "Hermes",
        "Dionysus"
      ],
      "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Greek goddess is associated with love and beauty?",
      "options": [
        "Hera",
        "Artemis",
        "Aphrodite",
        "Demeter"
      ],
      "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What creature has the body of a lion and the head of a human?",
      "options": [
        "Sphinx",
        "Minotaur",
        "Centaur",
        "Gorgon"
      ],
      "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is known as the god of war?",
      "options": [
        "Hades",
        "Ares",
        "Hermes",
        "Zeus"
      ],
      "correct_option": 2
    }
  ]
}